<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ConfigSchema xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns="http://www.sonicretro.org">
	<Groups>
		<Group name="General" display="General">
			<Property name="IncludeCurrentLevelUpgrade" type="bool" defaultvalue="False" display="Include Current Level Upgrade" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>When enabled you will not have to obtain the upgrade contained in this stage. For example at the start of Metal Harbor you will normally have no upgrades and need to get lightdash. With this enabled you will have light dash from the start at Metal Harbor.</HelpText>
			</Property>
			<Property name="IncludeCurrentHuntingLevelUpgrade" type="bool" defaultvalue="True" display="Include Current Hunting Level Upgrade" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>When enabled you will not have to obtain the upgrade contained in this hunting stage. This is basically the same as the previous setting but ONLY for hunting. This is useful if you have the previous setting turned off but want it on for hunting characters. If the previous setting is turned on then this does nothing.</HelpText>
			</Property>
			<Property name="DisableAllShadowUpgrades" type="bool" defaultvalue="False" display="Disable All Shadow Upgrades" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>When enabled Shadow will never have any upgrades in any stage.</HelpText>
			</Property>
			<Property name="DisableSonicFlameRing" type="bool" defaultvalue="False" display="Disable Sonic Flame Ring" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>When enabled Sonic will never have the flame ring upgrade in any stage.</HelpText>
			</Property>
			<Property name="EnableUpgradeRestoreOnRestart" type="bool" defaultvalue="False" display="Enable Upgrade Restore on Restart" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>When enabled your upgrades will be restored to the initial stage's state if you are holding the reset button while restarting. For example, on Mission Street you will lose the hover upgrade. Note: It is important to be holding the reset button BEFORE pressing yes on the restart confirmation dialog. Note: If the "IncludeCurrentLevelUpgrade" option is true, this will do nothing.</HelpText>
			</Property>
			<Property name="UpgradeResetButton" type="Buttons" defaultvalue="Y" display="Upgrade Reset Button" alwaysinclude="true">
				<HelpText>The button you need to be holding while restarting for the upgrades to be reset. Does nothing if "EnableUpgradeRestoreOnRestart" is false.</HelpText>
			</Property>
		</Group>
	</Groups>
	<Enums>
		<Enum name="Buttons">
			<EnumMember name="Y" />
			<EnumMember name="Z" />
			<EnumMember name="Left Trigger" />
			<EnumMember name="Right Trigger" />
		</Enum>
	</Enums>
</ConfigSchema>